every four years
each american voter has the privilege
and patriotic duty to decide
who is the lesser evil it's the question
that's been at the heart of our great
democracy for decades
that's why political scientists
developed a machine to assist with that
process
the evil meter intakes data on revolving
door politics
influence peddling insider trading and a
host of other parameters
so that every american voter has a clear
and obvious
[Music]
can we get evil meters that go to 11
those do go to 11.
hey what is going on someone get the
likes
oh come on you're fighting over this
again
isn't there a better way like what i
don't know it just seems like we're so
focused on the lesser part that we're
missing something
oh yeah who the fuck needs that machine
unity 20 20. let's try this without the
evil
you